Let's look at what's involved in a tune-up.
Say you've done all the little things you can to your bike and it's time seek some professional help in the bike store.
Our tune-ups here range anywhere from forty-nine dollars to about eighty dollars, depending on the services you need.
Basically, what's involved is a complete check through of the bike.
Basically, any tune-up will involve a wipe down of the bike, a clean of all the surfaces, checking critical bolts, checking your wheels if they are straight, checking your shifting if that is correct in the front and the rear as well as your braking.
Checking your bearing surfaces as well, making sure there is no play in there, no looseness, everything is snug and correct.
Then test riding the bike.
Making sure that If it works on the stand, that it works on the street with someone on the bike too.
Tune-up, pretty much is the total run through of a bicycle, to make sure it is correct from head to toe.
So if you need professional help, get a tune-up in any of our bike stores.